const mediumQuestions=[
    {   id:1,
        question: "What is 29 + 12?",
        answer: 41,
    },
    {   id:2,
        question: "What is 51 - 9?",
        answer: 42,
    },
    {   id:3,
        question: "What is 100 / 2?",
        answer: 50,
    },
    {   id:4,
        question: "What is 99 + 12?",
        answer: 111,
    },
    {   id:5,
        question: "What is 100 - 9?",
        answer: 91,
    },
    {   id:6,
        question: "What is 9*9?",
        answer: 81,
    },
    {   id:7,
        question: "What is 8*8?",
        answer: 64,
    },
    {   id:8,
        question: "What is 100 - 9?",
        answer: 91,
    },
    {   id:9,
        question: "What is 90 / 2?",
        answer: 45,
    },
    {   id:10,
        question: "What is 100 - 25?",
        answer: 75,
    },
]; export default mediumQuestions;